(フリド)お前が ソラか…。
会いたかったぞ。
So you're Sora, huh?
I missed you.
(ソラ)誰だ？
Who're you?!
Hurry up...
Get over here... Sora!
(フリド)早く こっちに来い。 ソラ。
Who are you already?!
How do you know my name?
だから 誰なんだよ！
どうして オレの名を…。
こっちだ 早く。
Over here, come on!
チッ… 何を企んでやがる。
What's he planning?
Contact
テメエ いったい 何を…。
What the heck are you up to?
なんだ？ このにおい…。
What's that smell?
(フリド)ハッハッハッハッ…。
お前にも やるよ。
I'll let you have one, too!
ウワッ！ アチチ… アチッ…！
Whoa, hot-hot...?
(ソラ)焼き芋？
(フリド)ハハハハッ…。
A baked sweet potato?
(フリド)ハハハハ。
(フリド)待ちくたびれたぞ。
I was getting tired of waiting for you.
あまりにも退屈なんで
芋 焼いて待ってたんだよ。
And I got so bored I baked
some sweet potatoes while I waited.
ハフ… おっ！
結構いけるぞ これ。
Oh! This is pretty good!
ソラ。 お前も こっち来て食えよ。
Sora!
Come on over here!
(ソラ)オレを待ってたって言ったよな。
You said you were waiting for me, right?
減ってんだろ？ 腹。
You're hungry, aren't you?
(フリド)うん うめぇ！
This is good!
うめぇな！
I told you!
Have some more.
だろう！ もっと食え。
におうな…。
Something smells...
そりゃ 芋 食ってるからな。
アハハハハ！
That's because you're eating
a sweet potato.
(ソラ)風が吹き抜けるとき
運んでくるんだよ。
The smell is carried on the wind
as it blows through...
キタネ様の隠し墓の土のにおいをな。
The smell of the earth from
Lord Kitane's hidden tomb...
この バチかぶり野郎が！
Blasphemous!
ハッ！
コイツ…。
This jerk...
出されたもん
黙って食べんかい！
Just shut up and eat
what you've been served!
そっちも！
４人のご遺体を返しやがれ！
The same goes for you!
Give back the four bodies.
さもなきゃ… バチ 当てるぞ！
If you don't...
you'll receive divine retribution!
ハハハハハ！
(フリド)バチなんざ 生まれてこのかた
当たりっぱなしよ。
I've been receiving divine retribution
ever since I was born.
だが 不思議と
死なんもんでな。 お前も➡
But the funny thing is
I just don't seem to die.
You should do whatever you want...
やりたいようにやらにゃあ…
人にバチなんか当ててる場合かよ。
It's not the time for you to be
giving people retribution.
フッ… あぁ やりたいように
やらせてもらうぜ。
That's right...
I will  do what I want.
だから テメエを… ぶっ倒す!!
So I'm going to beat you!
オラァ!!
うっ…。
なめやがって！
Don't mess with me!
ほら どうした！
Oh, what's the matter?!
《ソラ : コイツ… なんなんだ？》
Who the heck...is this guy?
(フウカ)あら… もう 終わり？
Oh, are you done already?
(フウカ)ちょっと
やりすぎちゃったかしら？
I might've gone a little overboard...
でも…。
But...
(フウカ)おこげを払えば 大丈夫。
It'll be okay if I remove
the scorched part.
You're mine!
(ナルト)もらった!!
Wind Style:
Scattering Flower Dance!
風遁 花散舞！
風遁って コイツ…。
She can use...Wind Style...
土 火 水 雷 風…
すべての属性の術を使えるのか。
Earth, fire, water, lightning...
and wind...
She can use Jutsu from
all the Chakra natures?
フフフフフ… びっくりした？
Are you surprised?
まだまだ 坊やには知らないことが
多いのよ 女にはね！
There are still many things
you don't know, boy...
About women, I mean.
Don't run away.
逃げちゃ ダメよ。
I'm going to tell you about
the mysteries of my female body.
このフウカ様の女体の神秘
教えてあげるんだから。
冗談じゃねえ…。 そんな神秘
知りたくねえっつうんだよ！
Yikes. There's a mystery
I don't want to know about...
火遁 鳳仙火の術！
Fire Style: Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
水遁 邪の口！
Water Style: Mouth of the Serpent.
うわっ！
クソ！ どうなってんだ!?
Damn it. What's going on?
やべぇ！
雷遁 地走り！
Uh oh!
Lightning Style: Earth Flash!
What's the matter, huh?!
(フリド)どうした？ あぁ!?
もう 終わりか？
Are you done already?
チクショウ!!
Damn it!
You've got spirit!
いいガッツだ！
それじゃ そろそろ
見せてもらおうかな。
Now I think it's about time
you showed me your true power!
お前の本当の力を！
And do it without using
a toy like this!
こんなおもちゃ 使ってねえでよ。
(フリド)ケッ！ ダメか…。
No good, huh?
(ソラ)待ちやがれ…。
Hold it...
《な… なんだ？ これ。
What is this?
Oh, but this sensation...
いや でも この感じ…》
そんなに オレの力が見てえなら
とくと 拝みやがれ！
If you want to see my power
that badly...
Take a good look!
そうだろう そうだろう！
Yes! Yes!
《フリド : だが まだ完全ではない…》
But...it's still not complete...
やっと やる気が
出てきたみてえだな。
It looks like you've finally
gotten motivated!
Do your chattering in hell!
地獄で ほざきやがれ！
いい風だ！
That's a fine wind!
(ソラ)獣波烈風掌!!
Beast Wave: Palm Hurricane!
(サクラ)早く みんなと合流しないと。
We've got to join up
with the others quick...
ナルトとソラが心配だわ！
I'm worried about Naruto and Sora...
サイ…!? サイ！
Sai?!
Sai!
(サイ)ちょっと
フラっとしただけです。
I just got a little lightheaded.
Let's find Naruto and
the others quickly.
早く ナルトたちを見つけましょう。
The poison spread faster
than I thought...
《思ったより
毒のまわりが早かったのね…》
What do you think?
どうですか？ たまに
弱味を見せてあげると➡
If you show weakness
once in a while,
you can get closer to people...
人との距離は ぐっと縮まると…。
I won't allow it if you say
that was written in a book.
本に書いてあったなんて
言ったら 許さないわよ！
You don't find the most important
things in books!
(サクラ)大切なことはね…➡
本なんかに書いてやしない。
You just have to physically
learn things like that.
こうやって
体で覚えてくしかないんだから。
You're right.
そうですね…。
《ヤマト : みんなは どこに…》
Where is everyone?
だったら… 影分身の術！
Then I'll use this Shadow Clone Jutsu!
チッ…！
おっ 風が… よ～し！
Oh, the wind stopped! All right.
…ん？
わ～っ なんじゃこりゃ!?
Whoa, what's this?!
よくも…➡
How dare you...
よくも私を殺してくれたね。
How dare you kill me!
えっ… なに？ 変わり身!?
Huh?! What?!
Is it a Substitution?
女泣かせの坊やだねぇ。
You're the bane of women, boy.
この長さにするまで
何年かかると思ってるの？
Do you have any idea how many years
it took to grow my hair this long?
髪は女の命…。
Hair is the most important thing
to a woman...
その命を傷つけた責任は
とってもらうわよ！
You will take responsibility
for damaging my most
important feature!
《体が動かねえ… 金縛りの術!?》
I can't move.
Is this a Paralysis Jutsu?
クソッ… いつの間に!?
Damn it!
Just like that...
Now boy, let's share a hot kiss.
さあ 坊や
熱いキス かわしましょう。
(フウカ)ただし 魂はいただくわよ。
But your soul will be mine.
く… くるな！
S-Stay away!
さあ…！
Now...
イテエ…！
クソッ！ ヤツは どこ行きやがった!?
Damn it!
Where'd he go?
何だ？ いったい何があったんだ!?
What?!
What the heck happened here?
(フリド)お前の力だ。
It's your power!
オレの術を弾き返そうとして
繰り出した➡
You altered the landscape
with the power you unleashed
in an attempt to repel my Jutsu.
お前の力が 景色を変えた。
これが お前の本当の力だ。
This is your true power...
これが… オレの本当の力…。
This is...my true power...
That's right.
Heaven granted you that power.
(フリド)そうだ その力は
お前が 天から授かったもんだ。
まだまだ こんなもんじゃねえ。
It's still got a long way to go.
It will become a much
more massive power.
もっと どでかい力となる。
あんな ちっぽけな寺に➡
So much so that you won't be able
to remain suppressed
in that tiny little temple...
くすぶってなんか
いられないぐらいな。
That's why you must seriously
consider how you use that power.
だからこそ お前
その力の使いみちを➡
真剣に考えなくちゃ
いけねえぞ。
ハンッ 訳わかんねえこと
言ってんじゃねえよ。
Cut out the gibberish.
(フリド)己の欲得
感情の発露に使うか➡
Will you use it for your own gain
or as outbursts of your emotion?
Or will you go beyond your home
and village and
それとも 己の家 里を越え➡
offer up that power for this nation,
the Land of Fire?
この国
火ノ国のために捧げるか。
…なるほど オレは
バチ当たりかもしれない。
I see. I might very well be
a terrible guy.
だが 隠し墓の あの４人はな
生前 火ノ国を思い➡
But in life those four people
in the hidden tombs
fought and died for the Land of Fire.
戦い 死んだ。
オレが その遺体を➡
If I were to say I was going to
use the bodies for the Land of Fire...
火ノ国のために
使おうというのであれば➡
I wonder if they would nail me
with divine retribution.
果たして ヤツら
オレ様に バチなんざ当てるかな？
火ノ国のために？
For the Land of Fire...
That's right! I will use this power
for the Land of Fire.
そうだ オレは火ノ国のために
この力を使う！
Who the heck are you?
テメエ… いったい何者なんだ？
…赤子のお前を
オレは 抱いたことがある。
I've once held you as a baby.
お前の父親を…
オレは 知っている。
I know...your father...
…なんだって!?
What did you say?
フフフ…。
屍鬼接吻。
Reaper Kiss.
《なんだ!?
What? My Chakra...
チャクラが…》
What is this place?
ここは!?
むっ。
うん？
N-Naruto!
ナルト!! アンタ 何やってんのよ!!
Y-You! What're you doing?!
No, something's wrong...
いや… 何か 様子がおかしい。
親父を 知ってるだと？
You say...you know my dad?
うわ～!!
Naruto?!
ナルト！ うわ～!!
うぅ!! ナルト!!
Naruto!
Let Naruto go!
ナルトを 離せ！
あぁっ!!
大丈夫か サクラ？
Are you okay, Sakura?
Captain Yamato.
ヤマト隊長！
ふん！
ジャマは させないよ！
I won't let you interfere!
(フドウ)土遁 岩柱牢の術！
Earth Style:
Stone Pillar Prison Jutsu!
あっ！
しまった！
Oh no!
フフフ…！
《はっ！ な なんなの!?
この邪悪なチャクラは！》
What?!
What is this evil Chakra?!
キャー!!
Fouka?!
フウカ…。
ゲホッ ゲホッ!!
アイタタ…。
Damn you.
クソー テメエ！
You jerks!
I'll give all of you
posthumous names!
テメエら まとめて戒名つけてやる！
ソラ！
Sora...
-Huh?!
-What?
なに!?
あら この子…。
Oh, this is the kid...
Oh, he's the one, huh?
へぇ… コイツが。
(ソラ)加勢に来たぞ。
I've come to back you up!
誰も頼んでねえってばよ！
Nobody asked for that!
You're the one who called for help!
お前が助けを呼んだんじゃねえか。
I didn't call for help
or anything like that.
オレは 助けなんか
呼んじゃいねえぞ！
I see...
そうか。 でも
来ちまったもんはしようがねえ。
But as long as I'm here,
I have no choice...
いくぞ！
おう！
Let's go!
Right!
Naruto! Sora! It's dangerous to fight!
Get out of there!
ナルト ソラ 戦うのは危険だ！
(ヤマト)逃げろ！
そうはさせない！
I don't think so!
やるしかなさそうだな。
ヘッ ３対２かよ。
It appears we'll just have to do this.
It's three against two.
It's four against one because
you'll just get in the way.
テメエが足引っ張るから４対１だよ。
チッ。
Naruto!
ナルト！
What is it?
何だ？
知るか！
Heck if I know!
(地陸)遅れてすまぬ！
I'm sorry we're late!
助太刀参上！
Assistance is here!
Chiriku...
(ヤマト)地陸さん！
(ソラ)地陸様！
Lord Chiriku!
さぁ どうする？
Now what will you do?!
(フエン)ぼちぼち いいんじゃない？
そうね
時間稼ぎは必要なさそうね。
アイツはいったい…。
(ソラ)オレが木ノ葉に？
うむ。
(ヤマト)ボクたちは
いったん木ノ葉の里に➡
戻らなくてはなりません。
ことが こうなった以上➡
改めて火影様の
指示を仰ぐ必要があります。
(ヤマト)引き続き この事件は➡
ボクたちの班が
担当することになるでしょう。
どうだろう ソラ君 ボクたちに
力を貸してはもらえないかな？
あいにくと サイがご覧のとおりで➡
復帰には時間がかかる。
隠し墓を守ってきた
火ノ寺のキミなら➡
サイの抜けた穴を十分に
埋めてくれると思うんだけどな。
別に無理に
誘わなくてもいいんじゃねえの？
ナルト！
(サクラ)アンタ少しは➡
場所をわきまえなさいよ！
ホント バチ当たるわよ！
(地陸)外の世界を見るのも➡
お前にとっては
いい修行になると思うが。
いずれにせよ
決めるのはお前だ ソラ。
《ヤツらの罠…。
あれは 地陸さんを
狙ったものではなかった。
ならば 考えられるのは…》
(サイ)へぇ～ ナルトが使う螺旋丸て➡
四代目火影様がつくった術なんだ。
あぁ！ しかも会得難易度
Ａランクの超高等忍術なんだぜ。
そんなにすごい
術だなんて 知らなかったなぁ。
あの術はさぁ
エロ仙人に教わったんだってばよ！
地味だけど すげえキツイ修業でさぁ。
最初にやったのが チャクラで➡
水風船の水を
回転させて割る 回転の修業。
その次が 風船を
ゴムボールに替えての 威力の修業。
これが なかなか割れねえんだ。
んでもって最後が チャクラの回転を➡
手の中に留める 圧縮の修業。
すんげえ 難しかったんだけど➡
影分身を
利用する方法を思いついて➡
みごと 螺旋丸を
完成させたんだってばよ！
すごいなぁ さすが…。
まぁ それほどでもあるってばよ！
ナハッ ハハッ…。
やだなぁ もう！ 言いすぎ
だってばよ サイそれはさ アハハハッ…。